heykatielee.com 2015-10-28

# Privacy Policy

THE SMALL CHANGE PROJECT LLC. PRIVACY POLICY

TERMS AND CONDITIONS

**BY VISITING HEYKATIELEE.COM, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY.**

OVERVIEW

THE SMALL CHANGE PROJECT LLC. (“Company”) is committed to protecting your privacy online. This Privacy Policy describes the personal information we collect through this website at HEYKATIELEE.COM (the “Site”),

Visitors and any users of the site are referred to as “user”, “you” and “your” and Company is referred to as “we”, “us”, and “our”.  Accessing this Site constitutes a use of the Site and an acceptance to our Privacy Policy.

On the Site, we provide information about lifestyle design and decision making. (the “Service”).

Use of the Site, including all materials presented herein and all online Services provided by Company, is subject to the following Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all site visitors, customers and all other users of the Site. By using the Site or Service, you agree to this Privacy Policy, without modification, and acknowledge reading it.

INFORMATION WE COLLECT

This Site only collects the personal information you voluntarily provide to us, which includes your name, e-mail address and credit card information, in order to purchase products or services. If you opt-in to receive our newsletter, the option to unsubscribe will be included in every e-mail.

We do share your information with trusted third parties who provide support in running this website including any blog or newsletter. All parties will keep your information confidential and will never be shared with unrelated third parties.

We may record information relating to your use of the Site in order to help administer the Site and personalize your experience by improving customer service.

Additionally, we may send cookies (not the tasty kind) to your computer in order to identify your improve our service. At any point, you may decline the cookies in your Internet settings. However, doing so may prevent use of some of the Site.

This Site may contain links to third party websites. Unless otherwise stated, this Privacy Policy only covers information that we collect from you on this Site. Any other link will be covered by the privacy policy of that specific site. You acknowledge and accept that we are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third parties.

SECURITY

We do our best to protect your information for any unauthorized access, misuse, or disclosure. However, you acknowledge that the personal information you voluntarily share could be accessed or tampered with by a third party. You agree that we are not responsible for any intercepted information shared through our Site without our knowledge or permission. Additionally, you release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of such intercepted information in any unauthorized manner. You agree to notify us for any breach of security or unauthorized use of your information.

CHILDREN – ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE

To access or use the Site, you must be 18 years old or older and have the requisite power and authority to enter into this Privacy Policy. We do not knowingly collect or solicit data online from or market online to children under the age of 18.

CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

You acknowledge and agree that you have reviewed this Site and this Privacy Policy and that you will continue to review to be aware of any modifications. Any changes to this Policy will be updated on this page.

Updated: JUNE 2015
